theukhighstreet.com 2018-09-01

# The UK High Street: Privacy Policy and Cookies Statement

**This privacy policy will come into effect on 25th May 2018.**   
The previous version can be found here. 

TheUKHighStreet.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: TheUKHighStreet.com. 

Our homepage on the internet is located at https://www.theukhighstreet.com 

The data controller for this website is TheUKHighStreet.com Ltd. a company registered in England and Wales with company number 4080769. 

## Information Collected By Us

We collect the following information about all our visitors:

  * where our users came from
  * which pages our users visit
  * which links our users clicked on
  * which terms our users search for on the site
  * the browser which is being used to view the site
  * the current IP address of the user
  * the time that the page was viewed

This means that we track how you interact with our site. This information is used to show you the requested information, for administration of the site, for one-time tailoring of the site to give you extra information about your current visit, to analyse users visits to the site and the way that the site is used and for general research and development of the site. As this data is needed to run this website, the legal basis for collecting this data is under legitimate interest. 

## Information Provided By You

There are several places on the site where you can interact with the website and add information. This information is provided under informed consent. 

For example, you can add reviews of shops and products. If you are not logged into the site, you will need to provide a name and a valid email address to add a review. 

We have introduced the ability to register on our site so that the site can be tailored to your preferences. The registration form will require you to give us contact information (e.g. your name and email address) and you can choose to add demographic information (e.g. location, age). It also enables you to customise how you view the site. Demographic and profile data will be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Social login: You may use 3rd parties such as Google or Facebook to log in to the site. In this case we will take the email address provided by the 3rd party to either match an existing account or set up a new account for you. You can also connect your account with social networks on your profile page. In the future this could allow you to use your social network photo as your picture on this website (not yet implemented) or even find friends from your social network to follow on this site (not yet implemented). 

By signing up to the site and providing us with your email address you are giving us permission to email you occasionally for the administration of the site. You can choose to sign up to other emails such as newsletters or alerts or private messages on your edit profile page. 

### How do I delete my account?

After logging in there is a button to delete your account. This will immediately delete all the information associated with your account including any reviews, links, saved preferences and other information on your profile. 

### How do I download my data?

You can request access to your data by contacting us. 

### How do I correct information about me?

On your edit profile page, you should be able to change all your information. If you find any information about you which is incorrect and you are unable to change, please get in touch. 

## Public Comments

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, reviews and feedback comments available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Who do we share your Personal Information with?

We may disclose your Personal Information to the following categories of recipients: 

  * our third party services providers listed below. These companies provide data processing services to us (for example, to support the delivery of, provide functionality on, or help to enhance the security of our Website), or process Personal Information for content customization, personalization, ad selection and ad delivery and reporting, measurement purposes or who otherwise process Personal Information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Policy or notified to you when we collect your Personal Information;
  * any competent law enforcement body, regulatory, government agency, court or other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary (i) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (ii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, or (iii) to protect your interests or those of any other person;
  * an actual or potential buyer (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any actual or proposed purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your Personal Information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Notice;
  * in order to protect the rights, property, or safety of TheUKHighStreet, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purpose of fraud protection;
  * any other person with your consent to the disclosure.

## 3rd Party Services On This Website

### Affiliate Networks

We work with a wide range of UK affiliate networks. These are companies which aggregate data provided by companies so that we can provide information about their products and special offers and show their banner adverts. The full list of networks we work with and links to their privacy policies can be found below under Cookies. 

### Disqus

Disqus is a commenting service which you can find on many of our pages. You can view the [Disqus privacy policy here](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy). 

The following services are all provided by Google. By using this site you are also bound by [Google's Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms) and [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy). 

### Google APIs

This site uses software provided by Google to show maps and extra information about stores. 

### Blogger.com

We have a blog at [https://blog.theukhighstreet.com](http://blog.theukhighstreet.com/) which uses the blogger.com technology and is hosted on their servers. Blogger is owned by Google. 

### Feedburner

Feedburner: You can sign up to a daily digest of our offers and new shops through Google's Feedburner on this page. In this case your email will be sent to Google so that they can manage the email list but we will still have access to it. 

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to give us information about the visitors to our site. 

### Google Adsense

We use Google Adsense to show advertising on our website. To hide advertising from Google Adsense you can log into this site.

## CORRECT/UPDATE

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Login and make the changes on 'Edit My Profile'. 
  2. Contact us.

Any disputes will be handled by applicable law. Any errors will be promptly corrected. 

## COOKIES

### What are Cookies?

Cookies are short text files which are stored on your computer when you visit a website. They are generated on the sites that you visit as well as by third-parties that websites work with to manage key elements of their business (user functionality and advertising, for instance). In most cases they do not involve or use personal information in any way. Cookies cannot harm your computer. 

They are used extensively online; for example, to store your preferences, keep you logged on so you don't have to log on each time you visit a site, and to provide hopefully relevant advertising. 

To place an order from most of the sites in our directory you will need to have cookies enabled. 

They are not used to share personally identifiable information such as credit card details. 

If you would like to delete, restrict or block cookies, you can use your browser to do this. 

We're giving you this information as part of our initiative to comply with recent legislation, and to make sure we're honest and clear about your privacy when using our website. 

### Cookies Used on This Site

cookiecheck | This is the cookie which remembers your cookie preferences on this website.   
---|---  
Community_Name, Community_Session| These cookies remember you when you have logged into this website so that you do not need to log in again every visit. If you do not wish the site to do this, you can untick the 'remember me' checkbox when you login.  
_ga, _gat, _gid| These cookies enable the function of Google Analytics Software. This software allows us to analyse visitor information such as which browsers are being used, what proportion of our visitors came from a particular search engine, time spent on the site. This information helps us to improve the website and hopefully your experience using it. This data can only be seen by us and never shows any confidential information. [More information](https://policies.google.com/technologies/types) about Google's cookies.  
fbm_, fbsr_| These cookies are from facebook - if you are currently logged into facebook they allow you to use your facebook login to log into our site or to add comments throughout the site or to 'like' or 'recommend' certain products or companies.  
Affiliate Cookies| Affiliate cookies are used to help us and our shops see which shops, offers or products you clicked on. These cookies are served by these companies:   
Affiliate Future| [Privacy Policy](http://affiliatefuture.co.uk/Legal/privacy)  
Affilinet| [Privacy Policy](https://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy)  
Amazon| [Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy)  
AWIN| [Privacy Policy](https://www.awin.com/gb/legal/privacy-policy)  
Brandreward| [Privacy Policy](https://www.brandreward.com/privacypolicy.php)  
Conversant Media| [Privacy Policy](https://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy)  
Ebay| [Privacy Policy](https://pages.ebay.co.uk/help/policies/privacy-policy.html)  
Impact Radius| [Privacy Policy](https://impact.com/privacy-policy/)  
Rakuten Marketing| [Privacy Policy](https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/website-privacy-policy)  
Optimise Media| [Privacy Policy](https://www.optimisemedia.com/privacy_policy/)  
Performance Horizon| [Privacy Policy](https://performancehorizon.com/)  
Pepperjam| [Privacy Policy](https://www.pepperjam.com/legal#privacy)  
PaidonResults| [Privacy Policy](https://www.paidonresults.com/privacy.html)  
Shareasale| [Privacy Policy](http://www.shareasale.com/)  
Skimlinks| [Privacy Policy](https://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy)  
SilverTap| [Privacy Policy](http://www.silvertap.com/Home/Cookies)  
Tradedoubler| [Privacy Policy](http://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/)  
Tradetracker| [Privacy Policy](https://tradetracker.com/privacy-policy/)  
Webgains| [Privacy Policy](http://www.webgains.com/public/en/privacy/)  
  
### Further Information

If you'd like to learn more about cookies in general and how to manage them, visit [aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) (opens in a new window - please note that we can't be responsible for the content of external websites). 

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This site contains links to other sites. **TheUKHighStreet.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

## CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us through the contact form

We do our best to make sure the prices shown on this site are correct but they are not live prices so please check on the merchant's site for the correct current price.
